Give it up for Monica.
Ladies and gentlemen, bring it on stage
another calligator
all the way from Abuja. He is funny. He
is spontaneous. Are you ready? Ben city
hero for Saki Dar.
Yoo!
Have a day day. I'm a day.
My name is
Eoo.
>> Happy New Year.
>> What's going on?
My father said when they do DNA test
that is why poor men they leave for God.
My papa telling me say no matter how
CCTV camera observe rich you know they
see rich man when they come up for hotel
with inside chick
something not square
is very sweet
like stranger especially the guest
I just
treat me like
And one thing when they do me for this B
today, I will never get I go to go buy
seafood or
I see goat meat inside
me. At one point give the woman the
woman say
when go
see food now go to join. So,
so waiting water can no be sequ
I show You sh
my deputy.
You know why they call my deputy?
My own state. We know they see
we know they see election
then they going give us man where be
woman as governor. I'm from you don't
know.
See
on your own
port
inside
you don't see person
you need
You never understand
poverty.
my way you go broke and you ask your
girlfriend whe
like this I must not marry I don't know
why big clothes get mar like me tangle
for bed because it takes two to tangle
I Saying girls as I was saying earlier
please I beg you stranger I if I fall in
love with you no they treat me like boy
I just fall in love with one
fellowship
as fellowship somebody be fellowship
everything
no stress me I don't like this
supposed be banker me I supposed be
lawyer supposed I put it to you my lord
but niger put down for my body
I know. So I start this work. He didn't
say I like her. My father look me say
how come my first son be making j of
himself. I said calm down. You go like
this work not believe. Last year June go
presidential go then pay me 4 million to
perform for 10 minutes. I nearly perform
for 4 days.
Poverty in a bust. You know say get
money give your family like this. Your
position for family go change you don't
know some of your family WhatsApp group
you are contributing nothing
you are a waste of space
that's why I send my father 1 million
when
I enter in phone my father phone face
off as he char phone call me for 2
minutes my father not talk I just hear h
now I say hello the best when my papa me
Look now my brother
God bless you now know me your son he
say shut up now begin they worry you
what you do for me brother video for
brother say my father was she don't see
my mama the best day I gave my mother
500,000 NRA cash as I give the money she
hold now once she look me say what has
this little girl don't to deserve all
this
you never say poverty
ban girls back to you the fellowship I
just now once bing just leave me say you
do me well but I enjoy do me like sh poy
I say I don't understand he say you just
b
so I like I hit something followed
everywhere
inside my
Say good night.
Ladies and gentlemen, we doing this back
to back. Give it up for another 40
comedian coming to stay. Ladies and
gentlemen, I bring to you poor joint.
YET, LET'S MAKE WELCOME ANOTHER FUNNY
COMEDIAN ALL THE WAY FROM THE NORTHERN
PART OF NIGERIA, SIRI.
OH, let's go.
Ehoo.
Good morning. Happy New Year.
What is going on? Very dangerous place.
Yes, I know what I'm saying. Those
people
over people, are you here? Your girls
is what?
That place
dangerous.
The girls from that place they are no
more. How you going to kiss girl from
Opa? She go get my belt for your mouth.
You're going say why you do like that?
The girl use say no mommy.
What is going on? You are welcome to new
year.
Everything where you do last year don't
work. This year you go work. Yeah. Amen.
I get why they pray for
and today start
hand touch everybody when I never say
anything. Poverty is not your portion
this year. Say amen.
>> Amen.
>> You see you notice when say people
regular they shout amen. Some of give
free ticket for they for
answer. Amen. Poverty not be good.
Yes. So you know say the things when
they motivate poor man different from
the one where they motivate big man.
Yes. Now everything they offend poor
man. I'm saying this to you because now
one crony poor man born me from
experience. Everything they annoy my
father check when two big men
they are happy for their fellow rich
people. That is why you see say the rich
will always be rich.
See two big men
2025 model just pass you see say oh boy.
See the other one not a bad one at all.
I like to add this to my collection. Two
poor men they inside pad 1998
model that motor pass here the one where
they drive
I beg
we hear what
money
then what's the other one I leave them
all this went get so they shop for
everything they offend I don't ask my
father this land for my where
buy my father just say I beg him what
what land be your problem
everything they offend po man
if you see the things where they
motivate big men that is why big men see
opportunity in everything look at this
country this country so far corona do
you know the big man saw opportunity in
that it is a woman think how to so face
ming that kind I don't talk and say if
rapture happen today all of us meet for
heaven god going give Every human be
opportunity to ask God one one question.
Say poverty the mind. The kind question
where big men go ask God. Even God
shock. Somebody like to own business. He
just look say my maker.
What will you question me to build my
own small heaven?
Even God shook. He say even if it's
heaven annex annex. You go see somebody
go and say my maker will you give me the
opportunity to supply dies with all
these small small hotels in heaven.
Somebody like come say my maker will you
permit me to have my own network in this
heaven. The first poor man when they go
give opportunity to ask God question
even God ask when I create this idiot
because po mind you go see person ask
make first carry hand up God no vessel
when you create human being who what
really offend you when you create ampit
no smell you
even this guy be like ampit don't make
and lose relationship first say God
He said he said I'm a funny guy. Why
they laugh like woman say funny guy?
Yeah. So I be funny guy to this kind
time 1 a.m. when casino no is this
casino very person I beg from 8 in the
evening I say call me now when people
eyes clear make crack joke he say no
hold on hold on b love you. I say no now
see 12 now people don't drink full eye
for new year I crack now so I start my
life they try make drunkard happy very
start
very bad way to start a year yes and you
know those of come from abroad they
leave show I see all of them pay one man
carry flyer for I'm going to use all my
money especially those ones where come
from UK they use all their money they
look person say Let's leave
now for this video. Yes. Now, so I thank
all of
this. I just got back now. We inocniz
tax. Yes. They say there is no money.
Where they are doing all of them buying
tables enjoying they will pay tax.
Listen to me. If there's one person you
must never offend in this country as a
whole collectively as citizen they
advisors you can offend nothing happen
they tell you free of charge if you
offend nothing will happen offend you
not do anything offend
we not try because if she just starve
baba one round It is finished.
The full destiny of this nation now just
for one round. And you know when de we
go feed the repercussion.
He said my wife was on her own for her.
Now
we get another one. You people
mama now she's not letting me do in my
bedroom. You will feel it.
January they will start paying tax for
their oxygen
tax for no reason just pay tax for this
country. The issues of tax has been a
very strong conversation recently. They
say that if we buy one liter they pay
tax. People look take risk. People
question
when one morning if you just wake up
just tell us fellow citizens
of the Federal Republic.
It saddens my heart
to announce that this country has been
sold
to Bina Vaso.
We all all of us contribute money to go
by the country. Yes. Because
very emotional person happy. Nobody
supposed to help you. You must call.
Hello.
How are you? Say your excellency. I'm
fine. You are fine. Are you happy? Shima
say yes I'm happy. You are happy when I
have not come.
Nobody supposed to be happy.
go meet Remy. He know they give up. Remy
baby,
you know that I was not the one that say
you are not my mama.
Now my mama be
my mama. So your mommy
talk about this guy me my brother. He
who is down fears no fall.
Yes. Now me fire take your problem as I
just reach you know easy to just deal
with you. The problem about you commit
offense they deal with you commit
offense for they put you for prison for
so by the time they release you to come
back you die for road. Yes.
show for screen in the fight they beat
people
for this kind
understand what mean
movie that I
immediately do
sound Fact now
buy ticket
real
everybody come with their tool
I never see when I never see anything.
You see I see some comedian come to this
place crack joke
as comedian they crack joke you love
because of your safety because you don't
know whe
because you know they
know what's going on. You think we are
joking with you
guys now this year not let anybody force
you because like I talk so the countries
where they motivate poor men they
motivate big men that is why poor men
get addage big men get quotes there's
difference
yes now if you see you say word you know
what I'm saying now check now some
kindage where you go you know say this
thing the journey of a,000 miles
begins with a step. You go say now who
don't tr within no good
big man they knock mic now now
don't do like that people use 4 days
they perform reach my you knock for 10
minutes you go say this join this comedy
they do some more bandit
for your own good check now when you see
big men quote when you see big men quote
you know say that big men don't come
anything worth doing is worth doing well
no be poor man think that
That was America's 26th president
Roosevelt. Poor man think that kind
children this kind where take from
inside again when make me arrest one of
my uncle that small [\h__\h] they big which
kind that
get where my
talk that I just
woman in the commod
husband.
What kind of advice made and take from
that one? You you just say you no I
think they motivate you this year one
one one one elderly man for our company
that time we just tell say give us more
wisdom now look small children they grow
now tell us
he said now when food they smile now say
what be the moral of this wisdom he said
no worry when you eat your go tell you
storyh
by this time
truly I leave stage no I never leave
this stage IH
for I mean I mean I don't do reach 10
minutes for wait I get another work this
is the only thing I do with my life
cracking joke my life is a joke Relax
DJ do that
for my brother beat you
know say this work for their mind they
think I like this work by right I'm a
graduate I start my year crack joke for
people now my father work hard
I tell you now now my father know if my
father work hard I go sit down crack
that guy knock my go make me
yes now when I start work my father
looked me say how can my first son be
making gest of himself? This is not my
plan for you. I said calm down. We
needed this work. He said shut up. We
need comedy work now go die next long
like that.
Now I say no daddy hold this work. This
now 13 years ago poverty I do the work
they going they believe in me. I do and
they go 2022
they call me to go perform for somewhere
for 10 minutes then pay me 6 million.
Poverty is a bastard. You know say I
nearly perform for them for 4 days. You
know 6 million organiz
you give your family money know your
position for your family when I receive
the alert happiness won't give him I go
[\h__\h] my father up today I send down 2
million for the first time in his life
man when do security 17 years and 8
month take up salary now 680,000 when is
he 2 million for the first time he pick
the phone in shock Then
he call me he say hello. As I just
speak, he say hello my brother. I said
no me your son. He say shut up now
speaking the worry. What you do for me?
So only brother one for brother. You are
like a brother to me going forward in
this family. The day I not say money get
hold on I leave now. The day I say money
get power say my family get WhatsApp
group when my father be admin.
2023 I come back from UK after my tour
now say I need to surprise this family.
Now send 5 million NRA to my family
account.
Now forward the receipt to our family
WhatsApp group. When my father be admin
immediately the receipt enter the group.
I just see admin left.
Now no be say my father leave the group
be the problem. My father come right for
the group welcome the new bread winner.
Now since that day my problem start the
day I say money get power. But when I
give my mother first 1 million for life
now I know who I be to my mama. When my
mama hold the money now look I'm n he
call me by my real name he forget the si
say ken he said I say he said I wish I
saw you on time I won't be in this
marriage with your father have a
wonderful NIGHT
is actually my in-law
>> ladies and gentlemen keep in mind that
the party continues a driveway. We're
going to have fun till the break of
dawn. And we have also received reports
and I would like to apologize on behalf
of MC Casino. He understands that you
came out to have fun and we are sorry
for the hitches. But rest assure that we
are going to resolve all the issues.
Let's get back to the phone. THIS YOUNG
MAN IS FUNNY. He's very creative and
he's a natural. LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
BEN CITY, SHOW SOME LOVE. MAKE SOME
NOISE FOR MC PURE.
>> Ladies and gentlemen, this is MC.
Hey, God.
By worship.
Hey God.
Happy New Year. DJ, you the [\h__\h] up.
as new year where they call me for they
play what be Christian song if I play O
play everywhere go high
that they get ginger
gingerh
everywhere ginger
Happy new year.
>> 2025 go rugged.
>> I pity patient dog
kill. You see this year if you knock
door they open for you. Pass window
pass window.
Call the country they rugged they go we
day prime minister of India come see
Chernobu he come with assistant Chernobu
come with your assistant they discuss
what they want DO PRIME MINISTER of
India assistant bro they write
everything where they say they want do
assistant no bro he know paper he not
write anything he know everything they
talk they no good one
If you right then sam
say no no no if they go s
you know you know who you follow
you just understanding country when I
know what happen for Ghana everywhere
Ghana send 12 [\h__\h] to Norway for
parolympic sport then sleep wake up they
not see one [\h__\h] which year they
don't see one People wear G legs start
to define [\h__\h] for Norway.
[\h__\h] see heaven
and vow never to go back to hell.
Government of Ghana send five
representative
may they go investigate where c go when
the five reach the loss.
Oh god I beg when I know what happen for
woman where they do contribution from
January to November collect people money
December now she say she don't lose
memory say she not they recognize
anybody again God I beg
say don't know her husband they say your
husband say don't know if my money day
with that woman she going to know me on
God she going to know me I give you
money January to nove November you know
me December you lose memory you go lose
your life
you crazy
for this country Nigeria don't rocket
now everybody don't know if you don't
travel abroad you go know what I talk
about Canada I go open my eye I see my
pick my friend s account balance pick
four years four years money they pay
from the day
free school to secondary
speaking from the day we born a country
they Nigeria from the day we born you
you they
Nigeria now children with 12 years now
don't they get BP our government need to
make medicine for BP free children get
BP them and their pap under pressure to
make
I visit Canada zoo if you see animal
fresh
I see lion lion they speak English
lie I lie
That one I lie
but if you see the lion fine big then
they give life goat as in throw the goat
lion te and chop you don't go bene zoo
zoo don't go from fing a dog
now me they tell the person WHY I GO PUT
DOG FOR zoo he said lion
meet go strain don't lose weight e I
said release them My lion say them now
before I command give the lion 5,000
may take se
our government release all animal made
them go back to their parents Nigeria
not be for zoo zoo not go work here
I say for just now lion zoo don't lick
mango for just
don't you don't go zoo
If I now go see lion they chop roasted
corn. I swear I near the lion. Lion ask
me where I get pier.
I swear go now go throw corn. He go
catch him.
He don't read everywhere don't talk.
Nigeria not get middle class again. It's
either you are rich or you are poor and
say if you don't get money people not go
know then. Know
people know go club now. Go club from
far. Bounce and go.
Now you go to tell your friend you tell
them about me.
Bouncer no poverty ID card. I see they
come know they see
poverty go they make you lose stamina.
You know feel wear. That's why they say
if you are broke dress where you get way
go dress. Devil go make her when he
sleep dress where
dressing get attitude he get power
they like big man life big man go buy
motor when he drive this way they go
just press remote just they go poor man
you try buy car at age of 55
first of all you know they trust remote
too small for you to trust
eh you By car after 56 years of your
life, you come they depend on one small
remote to just do then you they go. No
poor man as he reach where they go use
his hand central lock.
Then he go down back up with remote.
Then he go around the car. They check
the door one by one like who want do
sacrifice? God I beg poverty.
Poverty bad.
Not not the way they embarrass man for
this life. Like may your fellow man hold
your hand for club. They tell bouncer
he's with me. Oh god. Lero
he's with me. Then you come they double
confirm so that they not go forget you
when you want go peace because if he
piece if he don't come back now you call
the bouncer I'm with him.
Oh god.
We need to they need to try for Nigeria
that lion own they need to try release
those animal you know be lion lion they
powerful they say no matter how bush do
this one lion of each grass lion they
powerful so they attach unto God name
the lion of the tribe of
the lion of the tribe of Judah
Nigeria not get middle class again you
rich or you are poor if you get problem
with rich man you are finish because
they they reserve money for court case
then you you reserve money for your
destiny
2014 me and one big man get problem I
tell the man I will sue you and you rot
in jail but they give me more 600,000
lawyer say 150 I give lawyer 80,000 to
balance 70 we enter court I fold leg I
tell my lawyer fire down who are you
then case for my mind daddy I go win
then the next day the big man go rot in
jail I beg
I know say that they are junk case.
They are junk case. Two years my money
finish.
The man soon they carry me and my lawyer
go.
He go buy food for us give us transport.
Hey
God I beg.
Who send me?
Who has come carry me for back seat like
where they carry go day care I tell my
lawyer beam s don't they shame my lawyer
say maintain my ste AND COMPOSURE NO GET
MONEY they get composure beam
my LAWYER SAY IT'S TOO late to fail
idiot my lawyer go stay enter court with
wig they say I put it to YOU NO PUT THEM
again no put time
we go die no put
No
one put
I don't want get problem with people get
money
now they find money they give Bible say
money is a defense no be money
go they fight for you
that's why they say nobody play with
small pick come borrow money
pack of money they make person do like
mumu people wake borrow money as they
enter the house any picking where they
see they don't carry baby shark
baby shark I love you
>> all RIGHT YOU HAVE crocod
leader of secret court for their
where are day before where are day
before now
so My friend go buy my friend go buy
wristwatch for prepared me. So I buy
wristwatch for her
be home now prepared me get
so my wife say joinu as he joinu he said
every year they bring one f say December
he win
>> MC casino's game of jokes the very good
bad guys.
Attention. Attention. If you're not
spending money, go.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
DJ DJ hold.
Hello Bi. I calm down. I calm down.
So DJ I be not play again. Just the
small time I get use.
Thank you.
No.
So ladies and gentlemen uh bin people
thank you very much. Happy new year. Now
the second day this uh
uh
people wicked. Well well last year we
see they judge the matter. Last year
they poison our village. So as a
poisoner
when I let me man talk I can't leave I
get I get time
so
did you call they depress that c go hang
himself
so another they call for me that one
girl dobbl just they pass
just my section
I don't know whe
sir. Hello sir. This period they know
they understand what will happen now. So
we feel just day now they'll start 2027
election.
So now wait now because last year we
fear Nigeria how can a deputy governor
thief governor phone
last year for burial
they go swear.
So as they go outside for go
if you get give me a drink. So as they
go outside I want go swear boys they
protest we not go we know. So as they
protest police cause me they stop the
protest they cause me they just shoot go
up cobra where they going police go
shoot the cobra for neck. So that cobra
say not this protest. Why police? So
coron go to make remove the bullet for
me go bring n
and police report.
So my friend go b with hot water. So as
he b the f the pool go me b you with hot
water. So I go account for gt. I see
tire never say anything.
Oh
this ton rubbish tenor
I see you. So father Christmas come our
compound. s come
if I if I just talk I just believe say
rubbish I won't talk now that
they pay me for now and I they talk some
better better okay man talk one better
one so one boy name kazim so where they
work kazim they call meeting kazim
insult
insult the other work so kazim insult me
those workers
Kazin Kazin you insult to during our
board meeting like Kazin say that not be
insult say sarcasm say not be insult
sarcasm I know part of speech where they
call sarcasm so as saying speech I wrong
so as sarcasm as I tell you now sarcasm
this one don't see make sense
Uhhuh.
So mama go donate blood. So she go
donate blood.
The problem I just get with bene people
now be this one. I just they talk I just
believe say ah now rubbish. I want I
mean why people they perform here man
see check my time first. people they
perform here just now 14 minus 18 how
many minutes we done 14 that's four
minutes now four minute don't do now so
now they do election for data state so
they call APC bishop because the person
they represent APC now man so he doing
hand like this wide hand for for the
sign person so PDP they are candidate
now woman so they call the PDP sign
board opposite JPC himself the woman
he open hand like say they hug that man
so husband they pass that that woman
husband so my wife now say they go for
the party now hug they go up don't
forget sign say call area boys they call
cut the man that man way they call cut
the hand so APC go cut the woman hand
say they call they cut as they cut the
thing they affect Get the woman for
house because spiritual matters for this
our work. So, so they are dog called a
dream as their dog they dream. Say
their dog dog who wo wo wo the dog they
dream say crocodile who be now who they
blow whistle
now honorary they blow whistle. So I
blow for palace.
So now as the dog they dream coca go
tell
co c co c co c co c co c co c co c co c
co c co cod and I be leader of secret
court for their
where are day before where are day
before now.
So my friend go buy my friend go buy
wristwatch for prepared meter. So I buy
for her
be home.
So my wife say join Osu. So as he joined
Osu he said every year they bring one f
say December he go win cow. So every day
so every day my wife they bring one
phone one f January to February
to December. So our customer just go
because we write our family name for the
for the foul body. So re our f
mur native f. So now the woman tie rope
carry the f they pass go police
announcement anybody not shoot bangard.
So as police announcement don't shoot
bang policemen come our house call
collect four bangers from my brother
they go put out for pocket. So the next
day they go checkpoint as they
checkpoint he they stop motor he come
mistake go stop me as he stop young man
park there as I pack
hungry the policeman. He not forget
bangard se for for pocket yesterday. So
as he touch I still get four cigar for
for pocket. So he call carry one of the
banger lighter like say cigar me go look
or he say shut up there bring your paper
bring your paper he don't even want
listen to me now put the banger for my
call lighter I know when you light bang
I know they blow once so the time they
follow me they hold on like this the
banger they lie small small now don't
like reach where now I be go so as he
blow all of us call me I drive off but I
surprise I go they hear park there who
they tell me don't come for a point the
pass. So I don't know say as I come I
call who they tell me pack there I not
say the man tongue they on top of the do
for mong
they tell me pack there pack there so I
can't carry the tongue they were carry
any DPO tongue way lost but the man any
tongue way lost make call collector the
man still not be own so
with this few point of mine
I don't for this work see time 1:00 now
they talk to some of then ah man all the
married clap for only the married men I
beg it not easy a man go provide for the
family he go pays children school fees
the wife not the work listen oh the wife
is doing nothing providing Everything
the woman lack nothing then later the
woman go see say my husband is not
romantic person they do all those kind
things so he go get romantic go they
romantic is it possible now the issue I
face for my house with that I don't I
don't me I don't know say man on
Christmas day they buy gift they go give
your wife me I sab on Christmas day goat
we kill so the goat will kill the guy
they kill her now they kill the goat
>> because the boy is strong way well.
So the goat call get go get two
children. One of the children say get
append. So I
>> now here today I not well
that's 23 now. 23
I not do 10 minutes. Yes. Remain 5
minutes. Remain 5 minutes before I go.
Eh. So last week this one happened. We
go we go hospital you know say we go
general hospital I don't about but if
you go general hospital you go all those
women world especally those get ble you
see there men general hospital one man
very wicked man give two women but the
women not know say now one man give so
you know say women they touch each other
how how much how many months be your say
my own eight say eight wow 8 months now
be like this your big you how many nine
your own small you know they women like
themsel so the two women don't know say
now one but the children know so the
children
light follow the children know inside
they know say so one other woman the
other woman call they shop puff puff so
he not give this other woman so this
piko they lose as this man they shop the
food they enter so this [\h__\h] made this
woman give her that is fresh for give
another woman knacking hand that night
time the tie signboard from shop right
go pull for angle park. So as the car
the shop go the guy will fix eyelashes
for foul as he fix the eyelashes for the
nohere now wait 5 minutes I want half of
this all go before come
so my friend go buy disabled f the
disabled fa
so as they bring come
so that they bring a aa so
that in DNA A the other one as so
this guy not tire carry me come
never see anything
come I not say food bene here come worry
me come see all this dummy not be dummy
I mean man they call her they sell
clothes one guy they send man clothes
the other they send man woman clothes so
when they close they pack their dummy
for so as they come back they go I say
this dummy he go face this time what
they make say for night they pass up
they go meet this other do so after 9
month that call so I see
so I see G the one go 3 minutes so I see
G they call us and they said pregnancy
close so he call they call say children
clothes so I think children close one
day just see some children they go
school now he call they follow them they
go you you be human being say in the
night because that woman very wicked
inject her give her we so the do wear so
as do they go in calorie don't dry
because intestine they up so the photo
never dry now
this guy pity for
the guy not even know where to look
are Are you hearing me? You know they
hear me. Don't worry. As soon we
hear one thing
I beg. So lastly let me do this one then
I go because
there when I reach Lagos I hear of this
artist joke as I reach Lego say M said
talk. If you interview Malik say I
started from the go
interview a say start from go interview
B where start from go even whiskey and
they say they start from G. So now since
all the artist start from G which we do
environmental so I do environmental so I
small small some inside this
inside the go.
So,
so with this viewpoint of mine, I've
been able to
I've been able to convince you that
foundation is better than empty land.
Thank you very much.
Attention.
>> MC Casino's game of jokes.